Hadi Lashkari Ghouchani

Senior Android Developer

@ hadilashkari@gmail.com

+98 939 125 8116

O Tehran Iran

github.com/hadilg

stackoverflow.com/users/2482947 in linkedin.com/in/hadilg

Summarv

A professional developer with over 14 years of experience in software development, where over 3 years of his experience covers Android development. An introvert person who has profound learning and contributing

A Creative, value driven and passionate developer who enjoys doing math, solving problems and creating A creative, while driver and passionate developer will enjoys doing materials, solving problems and creating scalable, maintainable, and efficient apps to make the world better place to live.

A person whose goal is to surround himself with happy, creative, motivative and clever persons, so his talent

He's interested in Data Science and Data Engineering so he's looking forward to learn TensorFlow Lite as soon

Experience

Lead Android Developer

at Sheypoor

🛗 Jan. 2018 - Present

O Tehran, Iran

Sheypoor is one of two lead classified marketplaces in Iran with 1.5+ million users per day, 13+ million overall users and 344+ million sessions.

- Increase the number of users per day from 0.5+ million to 1.5+ million in a year.
- As functional manager of the Android team, I'm responsible for the code quality of the Sheypoor app. I coach the team to practice design patterns, clean code, and using app architecture, along with updating libraries and adding new features with focus on agility and UX.
- Implement new design of the entire app, including rebranding for summer campaign.
- · Improve the legacy code quality by adding Dagger and Kotlin.

Technologies:

- Dagger 2, RxJava 2, Butter Knife, Greendao, etc.
- Agile, Kanban, Git Flow, CI/CD
- Mockito, Espresso, Jacoco
- · Pivotal Tracker, Github, Jenkins, Slack, Zeplin, etc.

Senior Android Developer

at Myket

m Sep. 2015 - Des. 2017

O Tehran, Iran

Myket is one of two lead app stores in Iran with over 8+ million users.

Missions:

- Starting TDD and installing Jenking's pipeline to handle CI/CD.
- Implementing features such as handling deeplinks, search page, inbox page, etc.

Technologies:

- Volley, OneSignal, EventBus, OrmLite, etc.
- · Agile, Scrum, Git Flow
- · Mockito, Espresso
- · Atlassian Jira, Atlassian Confluence, Gitlab, Jfrog, Jenkins

Java and C# developer

at Soha System

mar. 2015 - Aug. 2015

O Tehran, Iran

SOHA was formed to focus on solutions based on smart cards.

- · Implementing RFID card reader Android app via bluetooth connection.
- · Implementing Android and desktop apps.

Article

ProAndroidDev post: Logging in Kotlin

ProAndroidDev post: Reactive MVVM architectural pattern
ProAndroidDev post: Loading entities from database and server API by using RxJava

ProAndroidDev post: LiveData with single events

Special Honor

Ranked 44th among more than five thousand participants in the National Graduate Entrance Exam in Physics

Receive result-oriented badge in Sheypoor at 2018

Education

Sharif University Of Technology Payame-Noor University of Mashad

B.Sc

in Physics in Physics

Feb. 2010 Jul. 2007

Tools / Skills

Android

Android Architecture Components/JetPack Lifecycles/LiveData/Navigation/Paging ViewModel/WorkManager Dagger 2/RxJava 2/Retrofit 2/... Butter Knife/ObjectBox/...

Architecture

Clean Architecture/Hexagonal Architecture MVVM, MVP, RMVVM

Principle

Clean Code/SOLID

Object Oriented Programming

Functional Programming

Stable Dependencies Principle

Stable Abstractions Principle

Design Pattern

Factory/Builder/Singleton/...

Adapter/Facade/Proxy/..

Strategy/Chain of responsibility/...

Android test library

JUnit/Mockito/Espresso/Jacoco/...

Build Tool

Gradle/Maven/Ant/Make/...

Command Line Tool

grep/sed/netstat/awk/docker/... adb/sdkmanager/avdmanager/...

Development Tool

Pivotal Tracker/Jira/Jenkins/...

Programing Language

Java/Kotlin/Scala/Pvthon Groovy/Dart/Javascript/Rust/...

Operating System

Linux(Fedora/Ubuntu/Debian), OS X

Language

English: Advance Farsi: Native

The source of this resume in github

Built at January 2, 2019